structube.com 2016-05-27

# Privacy Policy | Structube

**Last Updated: March 26, 2015  **

Structube knows you care how information about you is used and shared, and Structube appreciates your trust that it will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes Structube’s Privacy Policy. By visiting Structube.com, you're accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

### What Personal Information About Customers Does Structube Gather?

The information Structube learns from customers on Structube.com helps Structube personalize and continually improve your Structube experience. Here are the types of information Structube gathers.

**Information You Give to Structube:  **Structube receives and stores any information you enter on Structube.com or give to Structube in any other way. Click here to see examples of what information Structube collects. You can choose not to provide certain information, but you might not be able to take advantage of many of Structube.com’s features. Structube uses the information you provide for purposes such as responding to your requests, customizing your future shopping experience, improving Structube stores, and communicating with you.

**Automatic Information:  **Structube receives and stores certain types of information whenever you interact with Structube.com. For example, like many other websites, Structube.com uses "cookies" and obtains certain types of information when your Web browser accesses Structube.com. Click here to see examples of the information Structube receives.

**Email Communications:**  To help Structube make emails more useful and interesting, Structube often receives a confirmation when you open email from Structube.com if your computer supports such capabilities. If you do not want to receive email from Structube, please adjust your preferences in your email Profile, accessible from the footer of Structube's newsletters.

**Information from Other Sources:  **Structube might receive information about you from other sources and add it to its account information. Click here to see examples of the information Structube receives.

### What About Cookies?

Cookies are unique identifiers that Structube transfers to your device, to enable its systems to recognize your device and to provide features, personalized advertisements on other websites, and storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits.

Cookies allow you to take advantage of some of Structube.com's essential features. Therefore, Structube recommends that you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject Structube.com's cookies, you will not be able to add items to your Shopping Cart, proceed to Checkout, or use any Structube.com products and services that require you to sign in to your account.

### Does Structube Share the Information It Receives?

Information about Structube's customers is an important part of its business, and Structube is not in the business of selling it to others. Structube shares customer information only as described below.

**Third-Party Service Providers:** Structube employs other companies and individuals to perform functions on its behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and email, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.

**Business Transfers:**  As Structube continues to develop its business, it might sell or buy stores, subsidiaries, or business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Notice (unless, of course, the customer consents otherwise). Also, in the event that Structube or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will be one of the transferred assets.

**Protection of Structube and Others:**  Structube releases account and other personal information when it believes release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply its Terms of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Structube.com, Structube.com users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit-risk reduction. This does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Policy.

**With Your Consent:  **Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose whether or not to share the information.

### How Secure is Information About Me?

Structube works to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the information that you enter. Other precautions are taken to protect the security of your personal information that you share with Structube. Unfortunately however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while Structube strives to protect your personal information, it cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from Structube.com Services, and you do so at your own risk.

Structube reveals only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Structube transmits the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.

It is important for you to protect yourself against unauthorized access to your password and computer. Be sure to sign out of your account when you have finished using a shared computer.

### Which Information Can I Access?

Structube.com gives you access to some information about your account and your interactions with Structube for the limited purpose of viewing and in certain cases, updating that information. Click here to see some examples. This list will change as Structube.com evolves.

### What Choices Do I have?

As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of such Structube.com features as Wish Lists.

You can add or update certain information on pages such as those referenced in the "Which Information Can I Access?" section, above.

If you do not want to receive email or other mail from Structube, please adjust your email Profile, accessible from the footer of Structube's Newsletters. (If you do not want to receive Terms of Use and other legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Policy, those notices still will govern your use of Structube.com, and it's your responsibility to review them for changes.)

The Help feature on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the website of its manufacturer. Cookies allow you to take advantage of some of Structube.com's essential features therefore, Structube recommends that you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject Structube's cookies, you will not be able to add items to your Shopping Cart, proceed to Checkout, or use any Structube.com products and services that require you to sign in to your account.

If you request access to your personal information, Structube will respond to your request within 30 days. There may be a cost to this access if you require copies of records or if your request is deemed unreasonable. Structube will advise you of any cost related to your request prior to processing it. Structube may not be able to provide you with access to your personal information where the information cannot be separated from the records of others, cannot be disclosed for reasons of security or commercial confidentiality, or is protected by legal privilege.

### Are Children Allowed to Use Structube.com?

If you are under 18 years of age, you may use Structube.com only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. If you are under 13 years of age, it is asked that you do not provide any personally identifiable information to Structube without the knowledge and permission of your parent or guardian. Structube does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 and does not target its website to children under the age of 13.

### Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions

If you choose to visit Structube.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Policy and Structube's Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the Province of Québec, Canada. If you have any concern about privacy at Structube.com, please contact Structube with a thorough description, and Structube will try to resolve it to the best of its abilities.

Structube changes constantly, and its Privacy Notice and Terms of Use will change also. You should check Structube.com frequently to view recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, Structube’s current Privacy Policy applies to all information that it has about you and your account. Structube stands behind the promises it makes and will never materially change its policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.

## Examples of Information Collected

### Information You Give Structube

You provide most information when you search, buy, post, participate in a contest or questionnaire, or communicate with Structube. For example, you provide information when you search for a product; make an order; provide information in Your Account (and you might have more than one, if you have used more than one email address when shopping at Structube.com); communicate with Structube by telephone, email, or otherwise; complete a questionnaire or a contest entry form and compile Wish Lists. As a result of those actions, you might supply Structube with information such as your name, address, and telephone number; credit card information; names of people to whom purchases have been shipped, including address and telephone number; names of people including addresses and telephone numbers; content of reviews and emails to Structube; and financial information.

### Automatic Information

Examples of the information Structube collects and analyzes include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; email address; password; computer and connection information, such as browser type, version and timezone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system, and platform; purchase history, which Structube occasionally aggregates with similar information from other customers to create bestseller lists; the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through, and from Structube.com, including date and time; cookie number; and products you have viewed or searched for. Structube may also use browser data such as cookies, Flash cookies (also known as Flash Local Shared Objects), or similar data on certain parts of Structube.com for fraud prevention and other purposes. During certain visits, Structube may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page. Structube may also collect technical information to help identify your device for fraud prevention and diagnostic purposes.

### Mobile

Most mobile devices provide users with the ability to disable location services. Most likely, these controls are located in the device's settings menu. If you have questions about how to disable your device's location services, Structube recommends that you contact your mobile service carrier or your device manufacturer.

### Information from Other Sources

Examples of information Structube receives from other sources include updated delivery and address information from its carriers or other third parties, which Structube uses to correct its records and deliver future purchases or communication more effectively; and credit history information from credit bureaus, which Structube uses to help prevent and detect fraud and to offer certain credit or financial services to some customers.

### Information You Can Access

Examples of information you can currently access easily at Structube.com include up-to-date information regarding recent orders, personally identifiable information (including name, email, password, communication preferences, and address book), payment settings (including credit card information, gift certificates and gift cards), email notification settings and Wish Lists.

### Unsubscribe from our Newsletter

Click here to unsubscribe from our newsletter
